Kenneth Hill

Location: Baltimore, MD

SUMMARY

Environmental Health and Safety Professional with 4 years of experience delivering lean process improvement, root cause analysis, and data visualization within the supply chain industry. Currently pursuing an Associate of Science in Information Systems Management.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Amazon.com

Safety Specialist, Full-time, Sep. 2018 – Present

- Upholding accurate recordkeeping in accordance with OSHA record keeping (29 CFR 1904) standards.
- Contributed to process improvement initiatives across the Amazon Sortation Center Network in the states of Maryland, New Jersey, Connecticut, Georgia, and Tennessee
- Launched 3 Sort Centers within the Baltimore node
- Facilitated workplace health training for 100+ newly hired Area Managers, Operations Managers, and Safety Specialists.

Onsite Medical Representative, Full-time, May 2017 – Sep. 2018

- Upholding accurate recordkeeping in accordance with OSHA record keeping (29 CFR 1904) standards.
- Contributed to process improvement initiatives across the Amazon Sortation Center Network in the states of Maryland, New Jersey, Connecticut, Georgia, and Tennessee
- Launched 3 Sort Centers within the Baltimore node
- Facilitated workplace health training for 100+ newly hired Area Managers, Operations Managers, and Safety Specialists.

Maxim Healthcare Services

Onsite Medical Representative, Contractor, Oct. 2016 – May 2017

- Delivered root cause analysis and incident investigation to training to operational leaders.
- Partnered with site safety specialists to deliver conservative self-care awareness training.
- Converted to full-time Amazon employee following successful contract period.

EDUCATION

The Community College of Baltimore County

AS, Information Systems Management, Expected May 2022

Atholton High School

High School Diploma, Graduated May 2014